It's never too late to dream.
The First Grader is a drama, history, romance film directed by Justin Chadwick.
The true story of an 84 year-old Kenyan villager and ex Mau Mau freedom fighter who fights for his
right to go to school for the first time to get the education he could never afford.
Jane Obinchu, played by Naomie Harris.
Charles Obinchu, played by Tony Kgoroge.
Officer Johnson, played by Nick Reding.
Kimani N'gan'ga Maruge, played by Oliver Litondo.
Kamau Chege, played by Kamau Mbaya.
The First Grader is a 2011 biographical drama film directed by Justin Chadwick.
It stars Naomie Harris, Oliver Litondo, and Tony Kgoroge.
The film is inspired by the true story of Kimani Maruge, a Kenyan farmer who enrolled in elementary school at the age of 84 following the Kenyan
government's announcement of free universal primary education in 2003 by the late Emilio Mwai Kibaki, the third president of the Republic of Kenya.
The film explores themes of uniform, village,
education, based on true story, teacher.
The tone is emotional.